this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold watcher king of the
pirates lucky d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to
become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture
the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
this site can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course awash in danger and
intrigue the crew will cover path across the grand line to the new world
luffy was sent flying from the sabaody archipelago by bartholomew kuma after soaring through the
sky for hours he found himself in a kingdom inhabited entirely by women amazon lily after a scuffle with
the kuja tribe luffy escaped only to return in search of a boat
attention please the snake princess will now bathe
this is a huge bath
a man hey that thing on your back
it looks
kind of familiar
you saw it
heartless judgment margaret has turned to stop
this is the
Shroud yourself from his leering gaze.
Huh? No!
My secret is out. He saw my back.
Then we mustn't let him leave the castle alive.
Why not? What's the big deal? I just saw her back.
But you know, it's kind of weird.
I could have sworn I've seen that somewhere before.
What you saw is a secret we would die to protect.
Or rather, one that we would kill to protect in this particular instance.
Secret? That thing? Why is it a secret? Who are you?
Take those questions to the grave with you.
Love, love, beam.
Hold on, what?
It's a slow, slow beam!
No! It's making me slow!
Huh?
Love, love, beam.
Run!
Why won't he transform into stone?
Don't tell me he doesn't feel any excitement
after seeing me in the bath.
I am without flaw.
But that's simply beyond the realm of possibility.
The sublime grandeur of your nude form
can irreparably beguile any creature.
His fear of death must be overwhelming.
The impure urges within him.
He's a pitiful coward, but he's a lucky one.
You keep talking about dying, so bye!
I was just looking for someone important to talk to!
From this high up, he's out of his mind!
I've got him.
Now, pistol kick!
What the? They didn't bounce off me!
What kind of bullets were those?
That man is a dangerous intruder!
Kuja pirates!
Go forth and capture him!
Uh, yes ma'am.
A man?
How did a man even get here?
Who cares?
Let's just go and catch the bastards!
Right.
That hurt!
If you want to live, you'll do as we say.
Of course he will, Ron!
No man alive is stupid enough to defy the Kuja warriors.
He's pretty scrawny anyway.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
It is a man.
A real live man in our village?
I've got a hunch you guys are the all-woman pirate group I've heard about.
I'm looking for your boss.
Where is she?
Why do you want to know that and why should I tell you?
Well, your boss has got her own ship, right?
If I find her, I was hoping she might be nice enough to give me a ride to go see all my friends.
That's just ridiculous.
All men are forbidden in Amazon Lily, which makes you a trespasser.
Clearly, she won't let you leave here alive.
Make sure I don't.
Ha ha ha ha!
I can't let myself go and get caught again!
Let them go!
Seize him!
Rock it!
Ha!
What the?
After him, quickly!
You heard the snake princess's orders?
He can't escape, no matter what!
There's a man!
There's a man on the island!
A man?
The Kruja Pirates are trying to capture him right now.
We should pitch in and help them out, too!
You're right.
Let's go!
She's already put our land in peril.
To allow a man onto the island at a time like this smacks of insolence.
I've tried to hold my tongue, but frankly, I'm starting to worry about our future with her in charge.
Don't let him get away!
The Kruja Pirates are back!
And from the look of things, the man has returned to the village as well.
There he is!
Huh?
Up there!
Darn.
I really thought she'd be in the tallest building here.
Let's see.
If I was important, where would I go?
How did they find me so fast?
I jumped the whole village!
We'd better hurry up and kill him before the snake princess can interrogate him.
Those girls really want to shoot me!
He fell!
There he is!
Behind us!
Oh, crap!
Halt!
I'm so fast!
A pirate worth 300 million berries, but what is he doing in Amazon Lily?
I found him!
Sorry, I gotta run.
Thanks for the grub, though.
Hold on!
Let me have one last look at your face!
I can't hold on!
This place is freaking nuts!
Even the old ladies are strong!
Ha!
We've got you cornered!
We're too late.
The Kuja Pirates captured him.
There's nothing we can do.
I fear we must prepare for the worst, my sisters.
There's no doubt about it.
It really is him!
Get off of me, you stupid snakes!
What kind of snakes are these?
They feel like they're made of iron!
It seems luck is against us.
Let's just hope they skip the interrogation and kill him, right?
But they'll kill him no matter what.
Won't they?
It's with this country.
They weren't joking when they said there aren't any men around here.
I'm ready for my explanation now.
Specifically, I would like to know how you got onto this island and what you want here.
I don't know.
I'm just as confused as you.
I got sent flying through the sky, and the next thing I knew, I landed here.
An unlikely story.
Lying to me will only guarantee you an excruciatingly painful death.
You're here because you want something.
Well, yeah, I could really use a ship.
Actually, it'd be better if you guys could just give me a lift, though.
Either way, I'm in a pretty big hurry, and I need to get going right away.
You are the boss around here, right, lady?
So help me out.
I don't know if this disrespectful pup thinks he is.
The Snake Princess is right.
That story is clearly an implausible fabrication.
Don't listen to him.
He's plotting something.
You can't deceive us.
Anyway, I guess I should pay you back for all your help.
If there's anything I can do for you, just ask.
I can't rest till I know my friend survived like I did.
That's all that matters.
Because as long as they're alive, we can get back up and keep fighting.
The only way that you will leave this island is by dying, and your departure is imminent.
Please, Snake Princess, he's not lying!
Huh?
I know how this must sound, but I don't believe this man is the kind of person who can tell a lie.
What is she doing?
Please, Snake Princess.
I believe he's telling the truth.
This man is incapable of anything but a childlike sincerity.
I honestly don't think he would ever try to inflict any harm upon our land.
Hey, thanks, buddy. I knew you didn't really want to kill me.
You're one of our warriors, aren't you?
Yes, my name is Margaret.
Given that men are forbidden here under penalty of death,
he sealed his fate the moment he arrived in our land.
Why defend him?
Because I share the burden of guilt.
The person who brought him here and who allowed him into the city.
It was me!
Margaret, no! You can't!
Snake Princess, please steal your fury! It was not her fault!
It's true! We found him knocked out in the forest totally covered in mushrooms!
We thought he was one of us, so we brought him back here!
Sweet Peep! Afalandra!
We're just as guilty as Margaret, but under all those mushrooms, we just couldn't tell!
It was an honest mistake, Empress!
Stop it! I won't let you do this!
I'm the one who said we should bring him back to the village, not you!
Does she realize what she's doing?
She's trying to be honest, but she's just being stupid!
You guys are alright!
You were trying to kill me back there, but now I see you're actually pretty nice!
I bear the sole responsibility for bringing the man here, Empress!
Please, Margaret!
Margaret!
It's alright!
Now lift your head, honest little Margaret.
I have a soft spot for hopelessly sincere people.
Now tell me, Margaret, do you wish for my forgiveness?
I... I do.
You may rise to your feet.
Well, that's the snake princess for you.
Not only is she beautiful, she's also filled with compassion.
We love you, snake princess!
Love, love, scene!
Race, race, race, race, race, race, race, race, race.
What the?
Why didn't you keep quiet?
Hold on.
What happened?
What's wrong with you guys?
I turned to stone.
Why?
Hey.
Hey!
Hey, you!
What the hell did you do?
These three saved my life, you know!
Precisely.
And now they have been justly punished for their transgression.
Then it's my fault!
Wait!
Turn them back to normal now!
How amusing.
You think you can give me orders, do you?
Turn them back, dammit!
I believe it's time to release Bakura.
Bakura?
The man's already dead and he doesn't even know it!
I told you to turn them back!
This is the female warrior nation of Amazon Lily.
Here, strength is regarded as true beauty.
Show us what little strength you may possess,
and be grateful that I've given you death in battle.
Behind you stands the panther known as Bakura.
The beast has served as the official executioner of Amazon Lily for generations now.
When it's done, there won't be a single bone left to remember you by.
Oh my, our furry friend seems to be rather famished today.
Indeed, we're in luck.
It so happens that Bakura hasn't been fed in several days.
You should be happy, man.
Bakura normally tortures and toys with its prey first.
But he'll eat you in a single bite today.
I don't care about your cat!
All I care about is them!
Turn them back now!
Did you hear how that savage is speaking for the snake, princess?
It's Carolyn from Liv, Bakura!
Now, Bakura!
Eat her!
He's strong. He just knocked Bhakura out with a single blow.
And he didn't even use any haki.
That was just brute strength.
What the hell is wrong with all of you?
That woman up there.
She turned three of your own people into stone.
How can you just sit up there and laugh like that?
I never.
That little savage has the gall to shout at us.
Oh, don't let her to him. He's just an animal.
Sure, I feel sorry for those three.
But the Snake Princess had every right to do what she did.
Of course. It was justice.
They violated the law of our land.
But what you don't understand is that I'll be forgiven for anything I do.
Absolutely anything.
And the reason why is because I'm beautiful.
Just look at me. I'm sure you must agree.
Actually, you make me sick.
Stay strong, sister.
This simply cannot be happening.
There's no man alive that can resist my allure.
It's just not possible.
So long as that man exists in this world, I shall never know peace again.
How dare you hurt the Snake Princess like that?
Make the man suffer for his crimes.
Execute him!
Execute! Execute!
Marigold, Sandersonia, defend my honor and take his head.
You got it.
We'll get the job done, big sis.
So these girls have powers too.
Execute! Execute!
Execute!
When Empress Hancock orders her sisters to execute Luffy,
they transform into fearsome serpents and begin a deadly assault.
Luffy fights for his life, but soon discovers that the two women have a mysterious ability
that allows them to slither through all of his attacks unharmed.
On the next, One Piece, a difficult fight for Luffy, the Snake Sisters' hockey power.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!